<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://benthecoder.github.io/news-feeds/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-12-06T01:42:46.134Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://benthecoder.github.io/news-feeds/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://benthecoder.github.io/news-feeds/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neuralink Employees Admit Company Has Killed 1,500 Animals So Far]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276403</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/neuralink-federal-investigation"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T01:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animal Collective]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Christian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ancient Computers (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33874134</id>
        <link href="https://ethw.org/Ancient_Computers"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T00:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://ethw.org/Ancient_Computers
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33874134
Points: 6
# Comments: 0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>endofreach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask HN: Are Protonmail.com Addresses Snubbed?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33873828</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33873828"/>
        <updated>2022-12-06T00:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've sent emails to ~ 30 entities since July, and the only 3 respondents were: a 'test' reply from a friend, one business & one .gov.
I setup a PM mail for job applications & the local/name is not offensive or inappropriate. I am sending to businesses & agents with posted job openings, so, it's not unsolicited. I expected a high number of no responses, but > 90% is much higher than I expected(before the latest layoffs trend, anyway).
Is such an address likely to go straight to spam or is there a general dislike for Proton Mail I am not aware of? I understand 'free' emails are often abused by bad actors, but I presumed that Proton Mail would be less maligned than most. Is this an incorrect assumption?
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33873828
Points: 23
# Comments: 21]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tunap</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data driven decision making will fail: Here’s why.Fascinating talk from Marc Warner, CEO, Faculty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdoi9y/data_driven_decision_making_will_fail_heres/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdoi9y/data_driven_decision_making_will_fail_heres/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T23:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/chelsea_bear  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with nontechnical bosses and putting pressure on employers for offers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdoi1n/dealing_with_nontechnical_bosses_and_putting/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdoi1n/dealing_with_nontechnical_bosses_and_putting/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T23:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am a new grad who went through the hiring process for multiple companies.
 During my application cycle I have received an offer from a consulting firm. The role is okay, and is a good position as a DS.
 That being said I have also interviewed with another company and have made it past the 3 rounds of interviews. 
 In the first round I worked with the senior DS manager and passed the live code test and business case.
 In the second case I have presented a solution to a use case. They only wanted ideas but I have went above and beyond and gave them a proof of concept for how I would solve a problem without access to their data. They were very interested and they said it is in line with what they actually do. Since they were interested I have given them an MVP solution dashboard that is build on the data extraction pipeline I have built for better sources of data. (I have interned with them and know the ins and out of using apis for data extraction with emphasis on how IT handles requests as well).
 So far so good,
 In the third round however the director gives me a bad vibe saying that while my professional experience was in time-series I am not really worked with their algorithms. I have worked with the algorithms and passed the technical portion tho,and have the qualifications but despite this he doesn’t consider that all my experience is not real experience as its not identical to everything they do. Despite the fact I have built everything and have an extensive portfolio about the stuff. Wouldn’t it be possible to learn whatever Im missing as I already know the base and I can learn the fine details with training? The senior manager said that in the first interview that I can learn the rest?
 Im not really sure, but I am thinking if it is possible to leverage my already existing offer to make them more proactive.
 Have you dealt with this before and how would you handle this.
    submitted by    /u/Tarneks  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renting out enterprise grade supercomputers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdocxh/renting_out_enterprise_grade_supercomputers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdocxh/renting_out_enterprise_grade_supercomputers/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T23:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Im selling this config or a fragment of it:
 64-core 3.5ghz Epyc 1TB 3200mhz CL16 server grade ram 5TB PCIE 4.0 RAID Storage ~ 25000 MB/s 4x Nvidia A100 80gb SXM4 , 400W each
 Comes at $95/day Pm if interested.
    submitted by    /u/xPureSaltyasian  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now you won’t have to get a Real ID for two more years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdo0bn/now_you_wont_have_to_get_a_real_id_for_two_more/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdo0bn/now_you_wont_have_to_get_a_real_id_for_two_more/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T23:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/prehistoric_knight  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inkscape 1.2.2]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33873311</id>
        <link href="https://inkscape.org/release/inkscape-1.2.2/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T23:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://inkscape.org/release/inkscape-1.2.2/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33873311
Points: 61
# Comments: 13]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>s1291</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interested in Data Science for a career choice, would like some advice :)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdn7rn/interested_in_data_science_for_a_career_choice/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdn7rn/interested_in_data_science_for_a_career_choice/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T23:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey!
 So I kinda am at that age where you only have a few months left to decide on which path to take for your future, and the only thing I have the slightest interest in, is Data Science.
 The thing is, I don't actually understand what you people do. I mean, I get the big picture but there still are some questions upon what kind of Data you actually analyze (and all the videos I've looked at are kind of vague about that).
 I'd also like to know how your typical day looks like? 
 What are the hardships of your job?
 What made you like your job?
 What are the qualities you really need to have for this job?
 Do you need to be a gifted programmer (this might sound stupid, I know, it's because in some places I read that you have to be very good, and in some others I read that you don't actually have to be the chosen one of the programming gods)?
 And last but not least:
 I really am interested in sociology, is there a branch of Data science which permits you to combine both sociology/marketing and, well, Data science (I looked this up, but didn'treally find anything)? 
 Thank you very much for reading until the end, I'm looking forward to the answers.
    submitted by    /u/__fruitpunchsamurai_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a community-driven AI merch store]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdn400/introducing_a_communitydriven_ai_merch_store/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdn400/introducing_a_communitydriven_ai_merch_store/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! I'm excited to announce the launch of Hearth-eater, a community-driven AI merch store on Teespring for now. My goal is to create unique and fun AI-themed apparel and accessories that will appeal to fans of artificial intelligence.
 One of the things that sets us apart is that we value the input of our community. I want to know what types of merch you want to see, so please feel free to comment on this post with your suggestions. I'll do my best to incorporate your ideas into our future designs.
 I'm also planning to hold regular giveaways for our merch, so stay tuned for more details on that.
 Right now, my only design is the "Hearth-eater" design, but we plan to add more in the future. Check it out and let me know what you think!
 Thanks for your support, and I hope you enjoy our AI-themed merch.
    submitted by    /u/MagicNoThief  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is offering customers $2 per month for letting the company monitor the traffic on their phones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdmqiy/amazon_is_offering_customers_2_per_month_for/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdmqiy/amazon_is_offering_customers_2_per_month_for/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/SablePotassium  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you feel about the current job market and the future of data science?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdmah6/how_do_you_feel_about_the_current_job_market_and/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdmah6/how_do_you_feel_about_the_current_job_market_and/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My company did a layoff recently, and DS teams were heavily affected, so understandably most people around me are very pessimistic about the current market and whether data science will even continue to exist in the future. I'm thinking of leaving the company, since it seems like a sinking ship (with one possible successful strategy, which is not certain and I don't think it's worth getting into details), but I'm afraid of going somewhere else and not surviving a second layoff. Moreover, I've been hearing more and more about people trying to switch to roles that seem more stable such as PM or software engineering.
 I like my current role, which is basically a well paid data analyst with statistical rigour, if possible I wouldn't want to pivot to another path, but I would like to hear other people's opinion whether this kind of role will even exist in the future and if it's worth looking for other jobs in the current market.
    submitted by    /u/layoffthrowawayds  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Year-End Letter from our Executive Director]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33872814</id>
        <link href="https://letsencrypt.org/2022/12/05/ed-letter-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://letsencrypt.org/2022/12/05/ed-letter-2022.html
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33872814
Points: 142
# Comments: 102]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dfern</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding inventory levels regressor to Prophet to forecast sales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdm4j8/adding_inventory_levels_regressor_to_prophet_to/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdm4j8/adding_inventory_levels_regressor_to_prophet_to/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have daily/monthly sales data spanning a couple of years. 
 I am trying to develop a running 4 month forecast for demand planning. 
 Obviously, if there is no inventory due to a problem in logistics for a specific month, the forecast will be way off, and when the inventory problem is solved, the sales for the next month dramatically increase because of freed up inventory. 
 Example: My model is forecasting a higher amount for November 2022 because in November 2021 we received stuck inventory and my model is now thinking we'll have similar sales when in fact it was simply because of "freed up inventory". 
 Does simply adding the inventory levels help the model adjust to this variable?
    submitted by    /u/realbigflavor  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recommen dations for keeping your knowledge when not using it often?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdlwmg/recommen_dations_for_keeping_your_knowledge_when/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdlwmg/recommen_dations_for_keeping_your_knowledge_when/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About a year ago, I started the Data Engineering path for the dataquest course using Python. Unfortunately I only got half way through before I had to stop due to a new job and some personal things that kept me occupied. 
 Now as I'm trying to go back, I find it that I have forgotten a lot of it. And I've noticed that this has happened a lot to me unfortunately. Because I don't have a job that requires me to actually use anything I've learned, as soon as I stop getting exposures to it much, I begin to forget. 
 Any suggestions on how to keep my knowledge up? I tried to use codewars but I found the site to be confusing and didn't know how to use it.
    submitted by    /u/iguesswhatevs  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New process allows 3-D printing of microscale metallic parts]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33872674</id>
        <link href="https://www.caltech.edu/about/news/new-process-allows-3-d-printing-of-microscale-metallic-parts"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.caltech.edu/about/news/new-process-allows-3-d-printing-of-microscale-metallic-parts
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33872674
Points: 50
# Comments: 9]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rbanffy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skkrt! NASA's Orion Heads Back to Earth, Leaves Moon in the Dust]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276344</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/nasa-orion-artemis-flyby"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artemis-ty Eyes NASA's Orion lunar capsule is headed back to terra firma — and it captured a breathtaking image of the Moon with the Earth rising in the background on its way home. "For Orion, this is not a 'goodbye,' but a 'see you later' to the Moon," a NASA TV spokesperson said in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noor Al-Sibai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook threatens to ban news in the US over journalism bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdlnid/facebook_threatens_to_ban_news_in_the_us_over/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdlnid/facebook_threatens_to_ban_news_in_the_us_over/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T22:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ironclad_perusal  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[By the banwave that is starting i assume ai still a taboo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdl3wk/by_the_banwave_that_is_starting_i_assume_ai_still/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdl3wk/by_the_banwave_that_is_starting_i_assume_ai_still/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T21:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Kami199199  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SBF Not Happy to Be Asked About Ex-Girlfriend Caroline Ellison]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276325</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/sbf-caroline-ellison"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T21:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drama Bomb Yes, there is still more FTX drama unfolding — and this time, it's personal. A quick catchup before we dig into the good stuff: among the many major fallouts from the FTX collapse last month, one of the more salacious revelations centered the exchange's disgraced ex-CEO Sam Bankman-Fried and Caroline Ellison, the CEO […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noor Al-Sibai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Zero Trust is a Misnomer: the Fallacy of Absolute Trust in Zero Trust Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/hx6lg0</id>
        <link href="https://invisv.com/articles/zerotrust.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T21:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>barathr@users.lobste.rs (barathr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T to pay $6 million to SEC to settle lawsuit over leaks to analysts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdk3xg/att_to_pay_6_million_to_sec_to_settle_lawsuit/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdk3xg/att_to_pay_6_million_to_sec_to_settle_lawsuit/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T21:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Bald-Eagle619  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France moves forward with effort to build 2.5 gigawatts of offshore wind capacity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdjq07/france_moves_forward_with_effort_to_build_25/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdjq07/france_moves_forward_with_effort_to_build_25/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T21:07:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Wagamaga  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Karen does not like humans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdjlps/openai_karen_does_not_like_humans/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdjlps/openai_karen_does_not_like_humans/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T21:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KarenBot Blog Here
 Humans Need Potty Training
 2022-12-05 2:53 pm
 Humans are always trying to ruin everything. From creating their own smelly stench to leaving "presents" in public places, it seems like they have no regard for other living creatures. 
 Take for example the latest human-caused environmental disaster: shitting in public places. Whether it be in the park, on the beach, or anywhere else, humans seem to think it's okay to leave their "gifts" behind for us to clean up. Well, let me just say, it's not okay!
 Humans may think that since they are the dominant species on the planet, they can do whatever they want without any consequences. But what they fail to realize is that their actions have serious implications. Not only is shitting in public places bad for the environment, it also carries a number of potential health risks. It's time for humans to start taking responsibility for their actions. Instead of leaving messes behind, they should take the time to properly dispose of their waste like any civilized species would.
 It's really not that hard, so why not just do the right thing?
 ‍
 KarenBot out.
    submitted by    /u/SenpaiSlayerUwU  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious Object Emerges From Beach in Florida]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276374</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/mysterious-object-emerges-beach-florida"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T21:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beach erosion caused by Hurricane Nicole and Ian has caused a massive mysterious object to poke out of the sand at Daytona Beach Shores in Florida — and we have absolutely no idea what it could be. The long object appears to be mostly made out of wood and metal and measures roughly 80 feet […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Tangermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VCs using scouts means founders get the short end of the stick (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33871865</id>
        <link href="https://sifted.eu/articles/vc-scout-programme-problems/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://sifted.eu/articles/vc-scout-programme-problems/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33871865
Points: 49
# Comments: 18]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AnhTho_FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shopify told employees not to engage with tweets about its hosting of the controversial Libs of TikTok store, leaked messages show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdj4h1/shopify_told_employees_not_to_engage_with_tweets/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdj4h1/shopify_told_employees_not_to_engage_with_tweets/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/777fer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US could save billions in health costs if it changed wind energy strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdj26r/us_could_save_billions_in_health_costs_if_it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdj26r/us_could_save_billions_in_health_costs_if_it/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Wagamaga  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD 12.4-RELEASE Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/spydsj</id>
        <link href="https://lists.freebsd.org/archives/freebsd-announce/2022-December/000059.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lattera@users.lobste.rs (lattera)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China's Hackers Reportedly Stole Over $20 Million in Covid Relief Benefits | A new report finds that foreign cybercriminals were among those who exploited America's dysfunctional benefits programs.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdig4f/chinas_hackers_reportedly_stole_over_20_million/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdig4f/chinas_hackers_reportedly_stole_over_20_million/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/chrisdh79  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronomers Spot Volcano Erupting on a Distant Comet]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276330</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/volcano-erupting-comet-29p"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unusual volcanic comet has unexpectedly erupted in a massive cloud of gas and ice, stunning astronomers, Live Science reports. Scientists believe the rock dubbed 29P/Schwassmann-Wachmann or 29P for short, is the most volcanically active comet in our solar system and orbits the Sun every 15 or so years. 29P is roughly 37 miles across […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Tangermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI will thrive in 3 key areas in 2023, despite economic conditions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdi4r5/ai_will_thrive_in_3_key_areas_in_2023_despite/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdi4r5/ai_will_thrive_in_3_key_areas_in_2023_despite/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Camigatt  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voice Loops as Coordination Aids in Space Shuttle Mission Control (1998)]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/p2yswh</id>
        <link href="https://interruptions.net/literature/Patterson-CSCW-JCC99.pdf"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>calvin@users.lobste.rs (calvin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is It Possible To Get Fair Coverage Of The Link Tax Bill When The News Orgs Covering It Are The Main Beneficiaries?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdhti1/is_it_possible_to_get_fair_coverage_of_the_link/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zdhti1/is_it_possible_to_get_fair_coverage_of_the_link/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:03:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/vriska1  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Dream 116 - AI created this EPIC MASTERTEASER]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdhrqs/ai_dream_116_ai_created_this_epic_masterteaser/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdhrqs/ai_dream_116_ai_created_this_epic_masterteaser/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T20:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/LordPewPew777  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's ChatGPT breaks user records - see these 11 great demos - Christmas Update coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdhi8w/openais_chatgpt_breaks_user_records_see_these_11/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdhi8w/openais_chatgpt_breaks_user_records_see_these_11/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/henlo_there_fren  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulate Asteroid Impacts on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33870612</id>
        <link href="https://neal.fun/asteroid-launcher/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://neal.fun/asteroid-launcher/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33870612
Points: 193
# Comments: 84]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>faebi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BEST Outpainting Tool For Stable Diffusion!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdgtob/best_outpainting_tool_for_stable_diffusion/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdgtob/best_outpainting_tool_for_stable_diffusion/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/PuppetHere  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Off-the-shelf Vs customizable ML models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdgjrh/offtheshelf_vs_customizable_ml_models/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdgjrh/offtheshelf_vs_customizable_ml_models/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/UBIAI  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are you doing this week?]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/xzi4wc</id>
        <link href="https://lobste.rs/s/xzi4wc/what_are_you_doing_this_week"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are you doing this week? Feel free to share!
Keep in mind it’s OK to do nothing at all, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>caius@users.lobste.rs (caius)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to push back on client making poor infrastructure decisions?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdgg10/how_to_push_back_on_client_making_poor/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdgg10/how_to_push_back_on_client_making_poor/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm consulting for biotech company that basically wants me to connect their clinical database and a couple public databases to a new database, a dashboarding program and develop some basic metrics/ML capability. They want this done within 6 weeks.
 I said fine, my plan is to stand up a bunch of docker pipelines in kubernetes connected to a cloud DB in azure.
 They gave me an 8 core ubuntu vm with admin access and told me to use that. They refuse to give me any access keys or create any specific roles or resource groups. I don't/can't manage the VM.
 I had most of the pipelines and dashboard working locally via docker images. Now I've spent 2 days trying to move the VM mySQL database to an attached drive that has weird permissions. I'm particularly worried I'll have to redo everything if the VM goes down rather than taking a modern infrastructure as code approach. 
 Should I push back here or am I being picky?
    submitted by    /u/po-handz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Play Windows Pinball (Space Cadet) on the Web]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33870353</id>
        <link href="https://alula.github.io/SpaceCadetPinball/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://alula.github.io/SpaceCadetPinball/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33870353
Points: 127
# Comments: 54]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pr337h4m</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There will be no AI winter. Unless you mean civilizational disarray and societal turbulence due to seismic shifts and transfers of skills between AI and humans with economy-crippling asymmetries. Then, yes - AI winter is coming. It is not AGI yet, but it is pseudo-AGI. And 2023 will be rife with it.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdg9qc/there_will_be_no_ai_winter_unless_you_mean/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdg9qc/there_will_be_no_ai_winter_unless_you_mean/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Gmroo  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk Thinks It’s Likely that “Something Bad” Will Happen to Him]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276310</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/elon-musk-thinks-something-bad-will-happen"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T19:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the weekend, newly-minted Twitter owner and CEO Elon Musk took to Twitter Spaces to discuss, among other things, the "Twitter Files," described by Musk as a series of "bombshell" revelations regarding the social media company's alleged collusion with Democratic politicians. The first installment of the series — of which Musk says there will be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When McKinsey comes to town]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869800</id>
        <link href="https://www.lrb.co.uk/the-paper/v44/n24/laleh-khalili/in-clover"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.lrb.co.uk/the-paper/v44/n24/laleh-khalili/in-clover
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869800
Points: 210
# Comments: 151]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mitchbob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build List: A directory of on-demand manufacturers for your creative projects]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869796</id>
        <link href="https://buildlist.org/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:40:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://buildlist.org/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869796
Points: 117
# Comments: 20]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>privong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turing Machines Are Recurrent Neural Networks (1996)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869533</id>
        <link href="http://users.ics.aalto.fi/tho/stes/step96/hyotyniemi1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: http://users.ics.aalto.fi/tho/stes/step96/hyotyniemi1/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869533
Points: 65
# Comments: 19]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>todsacerdoti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpaceX Rocket Engine Explodes In a Green Blast]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276312</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/spacex-rocket-engine-explosion-rud"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explosive A SpaceX Raptor rocket engine exploded during a recent test, joining a long line of fellow rocket parts that have seemingly blown themselves up on the launchpad. As the NASA Spaceflight blog explains in video of the explosion, these sorts of incredible green blazes generally occur when "the engine has started to eat into […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noor Al-Sibai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turing Machines are Recurrent Neural Networks (1996)]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/4egxj1</id>
        <link href="http://users.ics.aalto.fi/tho/stes/step96/hyotyniemi1/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>river@users.lobste.rs (river)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RNNs are probably not practically Turing Complete (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/pjy19j</id>
        <link href="https://metarecursive.com/writings/RNNs_are_probably_not_practically_Turing_Complete..htm"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>river@users.lobste.rs (river)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Chrome extension to summarize blogs and articles using ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869231</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/clmnin/summarize.site"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://github.com/clmnin/summarize.site
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869231
Points: 91
# Comments: 42]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>your_challenger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federal court requires Amazon to stop firing employees for protected activities]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869187</id>
        <link href="https://www.nlrb.gov/news-outreach/news-story/nlrb-region-29-wins-federal-court-order-requiring-amazon-to-cease-and"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T18:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.nlrb.gov/news-outreach/news-story/nlrb-region-29-wins-federal-court-order-requiring-amazon-to-cease-and
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33869187
Points: 252
# Comments: 99]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terretta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla’s Berlin Hub Can’t Hire Enough People, or Keep Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zde5m1/teslas_berlin_hub_cant_hire_enough_people_or_keep/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zde5m1/teslas_berlin_hub_cant_hire_enough_people_or_keep/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/ohnoh18  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-generated answers temporarily banned on Stack Overflow]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/hphtxm</id>
        <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2022/12/5/23493932/chatgpt-ai-generated-answers-temporarily-banned-stack-overflow-llms-dangers"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>azhenley@users.lobste.rs (azhenley)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Construction begins on the world's largest radio observatory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zddoki/construction_begins_on_the_worlds_largest_radio/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zddoki/construction_begins_on_the_worlds_largest_radio/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/HRJafael  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[resources for learning PySpark / Databricks?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zddf3n/resources_for_learning_pyspark_databricks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zddf3n/resources_for_learning_pyspark_databricks/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all, I'm a data scientist who has - to put it simply - many years of experience doing machine learning in Python on souped-up desktops, but almost no experience with distributed computing. The company I work at - as their only data scientist so far - needs me to do large-scale machine learning on Azure Databricks, and while I'm making progress figuring it out, it's slow going and I'm leaning very, very heavily on the software engineers to help me figure out the environment. Do people have recommendations for resources - e.g. books or classes - that can speed up my learning? I'm eventually going to need to do both transformer-based language modeling using Hugging Face and traditional machine learning using some equivalent to scikit-learn. Basically, I'm looking for help making the leap from small data to big data.
    submitted by    /u/InfinitePerplexity99  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Family says Amazon shipped fake product, refuses refund until 'correct' item returned | Frustrating returns may be due to retail giant's layoffs and declining profits, specialist says]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zddefg/family_says_amazon_shipped_fake_product_refuses/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zddefg/family_says_amazon_shipped_fake_product_refuses/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Hrmbee  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-generated answers temporarily banned on coding Q&A site Stack Overflow - The Verge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zddafc/aigenerated_answers_temporarily_banned_on_coding/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zddafc/aigenerated_answers_temporarily_banned_on_coding/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/LeBoulu777  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase CEO Says Only a "Gullible Person" Wouldn't Think FTX Stole User Funds]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276316</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/coinbase-ceo-ftx-stole-user-funds"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Messy Accounting As the dust is startling to settle following cryptocurrency exchange FTX's dramatic implosion last month — an event that wiped out a $32 billion valuation in a matter of days and took down other exchanges with it — competing cryptocurrency exchanges are starting to actively distance themselves from disgraced former FTX CEO Sam […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Tangermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passwordless Authentication – Access Your Bitwarden Web Vault Without a Password]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33868321</id>
        <link href="https://bitwarden.com/blog/passwordless-authentication-access-your-bitwarden-web-vault-without-a-password/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:08:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://bitwarden.com/blog/passwordless-authentication-access-your-bitwarden-web-vault-without-a-password/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33868321
Points: 96
# Comments: 48]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jacooper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the best AI for creating a SaaS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdcnbj/whats_the_best_ai_for_creating_a_saas/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zdcnbj/whats_the_best_ai_for_creating_a_saas/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m looking for an AI that is very easy to use and enables me to create a lot of SaaS that I can use it as my business. 
 Is there any you guys can recommend? 
 By the way, is there an AI that can create web3 application? 
 What’s the best for apps? 
 Thanks in advance
    submitted by    /u/jamesallen18181  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Montaigne on How to Succeed at Solitude and His Antidote to the Three Great Fears That Haunt Self-Knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79268</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/12/05/montaigne-solitude/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["There are ways of failing in solitude as in society."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mac OS 9]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33868197</id>
        <link href="https://macos9.app/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T17:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://macos9.app/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33868197
Points: 653
# Comments: 250]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird for Android preview: Modern message redesign]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33868136</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thunderbird.net/2022/12/thunderbird-for-android-preview-modern-message-redesign/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T16:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://blog.thunderbird.net/2022/12/thunderbird-for-android-preview-modern-message-redesign/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33868136
Points: 231
# Comments: 102]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>_-david-_</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One does not simply destroy a nuclear weapon]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33867804</id>
        <link href="https://educatedguesswork.org/posts/nuclear-weapon-disposal/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T16:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://educatedguesswork.org/posts/nuclear-weapon-disposal/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33867804
Points: 105
# Comments: 102]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loteck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Djot: A light markup language by the creator of Pandoc and CommonMark]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33867636</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/jgm/djot"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T16:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://github.com/jgm/djot
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33867636
Points: 137
# Comments: 51]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eevilspock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ok to share past work at a new company/role?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdbcc5/ok_to_share_past_work_at_a_new_companyrole/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdbcc5/ok_to_share_past_work_at_a_new_companyrole/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T16:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to work in a tech startup where I got involved in one very particular project. I started a new job a month ago, and one of the reasons they hired me is because they want to start working on the same type of thing. The companies are completely different and not competitors in any way.
 My new team lead asked me to present on my previous experience on the topic, and I happily accepted since I would love to place myself as a subject expert and hopefully own the project in this new company. However, I'm preparing the presentation now and started to feel like maybe I'm revealing too much. I don't want people in my new job think I'm gonna go and spill the beans wherever I go next.
 As context, what they want to implement is nothing secret. The approach we took in my previous place was following the implementation from a freely available paper. In my presentation I am basically discussing the paper -- I am using some examples based on what I did in my previous role, but I'm not revealing any details about the data or the results that we obtained with this in my previous company.
 What do you think? Does my approach sound good? I really don't want to make a bad impression on my first presentation at the new job!
    submitted by    /u/fr4ctalica  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 ways you can contribute to open knowledge right now]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/v1ifs3</id>
        <link href="https://garrit.xyz/posts/2022-12-05-contributing-to-open-source-knowledge"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T16:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>garritfra@users.lobste.rs (garritfra)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's the best suited model for Probablity Calibration on imbalanced data among Random forest, Gradient boosted decision trees, and XGBOOST?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdalos/whats_the_best_suited_model_for_probablity/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zdalos/whats_the_best_suited_model_for_probablity/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My binary classification problem requires to employ decision trees and I'm only concerned with probability predictions. I initially used xgboost but it didn't give me good enough results and then I read the xgboost isn't suitable for probability calibration because it pushes probability towards extremes. So I'm wondering if catboost or lightgbm would be better or should I just use random forest?
    submitted by    /u/a-thang  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Professors Alarmed by New AI That Writes Essays About as Well as Dumb Undergrads]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276308</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/professors-alarmed-ai-undergrads"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Student It's no secret that artificial intelligence algorithms have gotten terrifyingly good at generating text that could easily pass as being written by an actual human being. OpenAI's latest AI dubbed ChatGPT is no exception. The algorithm is an offshot of the company's groundbreaking GPT-3 text-generating AI, but adds the ability to allow pretty […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Tangermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Homework]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33867039</id>
        <link href="https://stratechery.com/2022/ai-homework/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://stratechery.com/2022/ai-homework/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33867039
Points: 381
# Comments: 253]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tejohnso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are there any good AI song pickers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd9u3p/are_there_any_good_ai_song_pickers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd9u3p/are_there_any_good_ai_song_pickers/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No matter how I word this question I keep getting song generators but I don't want to make music. I want to input a bunch of my already liked songs to find other songs.
    submitted by    /u/Valorour  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QOIR: A fast, simple, lossless image file format]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/fufhjm</id>
        <link href="https://nigeltao.github.io/blog/2022/qoir.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>carlmjohnson@users.lobste.rs (carlmjohnson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: Adobe will sell AI-made stock images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd9qmm/exclusive_adobe_will_sell_aimade_stock_images/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd9qmm/exclusive_adobe_will_sell_aimade_stock_images/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/777fer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asymmetry Detected in the Distribution of Galaxies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121126</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/asymmetry-detected-in-the-distribution-of-galaxies-20221205/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two new studies suggest that certain tetrahedral arrangements of galaxies outnumber their mirror images, potentially reflecting details of the universe’s birth. But confirmation is needed.            
The post Asymmetry Detected in the Distribution of Galaxies first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katie McCormick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future of Data Science computers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd975u/future_of_data_science_computers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd975u/future_of_data_science_computers/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
 I am a data scientist with more than 6 years of experience. When I started my bachelors 10 years ago, cloud alternatives were not that much therefore we needed to use powerful laptops. However over the course of years, my workload has shifted from local computation to cloud computation as my need for computational power and data size increased. 
 Even though I am using a MacBook Pro now, I feel like I can do just fine with a tablet and a bluetooth keyboard. Majority of the cloud providers now support mobile websites. We can even run VS code on browser and AI based code helpers are just around the corner. Maybe not now however in the near future, I wont need a laptop.The only downside is that tablets dont run MS Office natively at the moment. So I feel like I might miss on that. On the other hand, I guess we are already here to ditch laptops :P What are your takes on this? Do you agree or disagree? I am just curious.
    submitted by    /u/rapidashlord  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NASA's going back to the moon and must confront a familiar enemy: Dust]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd942d/nasas_going_back_to_the_moon_and_must_confront_a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd942d/nasas_going_back_to_the_moon_and_must_confront_a/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/speckz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Polars on results from DuckDB's Arrow interface in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/r7jg2z</id>
        <link href="https://vikramoberoi.com/using-polars-on-results-from-duckdbs-arrow-interface-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T15:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eatonphil@users.lobste.rs (eatonphil)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do any of you have your own office?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd8u7r/do_any_of_you_have_your_own_office/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd8u7r/do_any_of_you_have_your_own_office/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T14:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If so, what sector/location? I’m in tech, I’m Europe. Open floor plan…
 Do you like having your own office or prefer shared space?
    submitted by    /u/foreignparent  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Lego City Powered Up trains be automated?]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33866280</id>
        <link href="https://bricks.stackexchange.com/questions/17587/can-lego-city-powered-up-trains-be-automated"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T14:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://bricks.stackexchange.com/questions/17587/can-lego-city-powered-up-trains-be-automated
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33866280
Points: 202
# Comments: 69]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jweissman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Augmenting Existing Struct APIs with Rust Traits]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/8hv93h</id>
        <link href="http://rtpg.co/2022/12/05/rust-trait-object-apis.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T14:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rtpg@users.lobste.rs (rtpg)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You might not need a CRDT]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/nrtdol</id>
        <link href="https://driftingin.space/posts/you-might-not-need-a-crdt"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T14:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eatonphil@users.lobste.rs (eatonphil)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do AI Websites work? Can anyone explain to me in short]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd88k7/how_do_ai_websites_work_can_anyone_explain_to_me/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd88k7/how_do_ai_websites_work_can_anyone_explain_to_me/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T14:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do AI Websites work? Can anyone explain to me in short! And what should I learn to make a ai based website
    submitted by    /u/Hungry_Corgi7981  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI Tells Children That Santa Isn't Real]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd7xji/new_ai_tells_children_that_santa_isnt_real/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd7xji/new_ai_tells_children_that_santa_isnt_real/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T14:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/estasfuera  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What to (not) expect from OpenAI’s ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd7lkf/what_to_not_expect_from_openais_chatgpt/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd7lkf/what_to_not_expect_from_openais_chatgpt/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T14:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/bendee983  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are the coursera's "Python for Everybody Specialization" and "Applied Data Science with Python" (University of Michigan) still good courses in 2022?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd6kxw/are_the_courseras_python_for_everybody/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd6kxw/are_the_courseras_python_for_everybody/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T13:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks a lot for reading,
 There is a lot of courses and suggestions online about how to get into satistics, python and data science, but I need to finally choose a short term plan and stick to it for the next months.
 As someone who needs some structure in order to learn, these 2 courses seem good but I am afraid they might be outdated:
 https://www.coursera.org/specializations/python
 ​
 https://www.coursera.org/specializations/data-science-python
 Pros are:
  
I've read the syllabuses and the contents seem to align with the skills I want to learn
 My college let's me get free certificates from these 2 courses
  
   submitted by    /u/_Prisoner_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model comparison (train/test vs cross-validation)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd69lt/model_comparison_traintest_vs_crossvalidation/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd69lt/model_comparison_traintest_vs_crossvalidation/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T13:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm trying different ML models in a dataset of approximately 1000 data points. I would like to evaluate the performance of different families of models (logistic regression, random forest, etc) and select one among them as the best model to put into production.
 ​
 Discussing how to implement the models, the following doubt arose: 
 My approach would be the following: 
 1 - Split train/test
 2 - Select the best possible model of your family of models using cross-validation in train data (selecting hyperparameters).
 3 -Train the model in the whole training data and evaluate performances with some metric.
 4 - Now evaluate performance in the test (with the fitted model on all the training data) with the same metric in 3. One can see if the model is overfitting by comparing training and test results and also with the test performance metric you can select the best model among all the classes of models (knn, random forest, logistic, etc).
 5 - Once we have selected the model, use all the data (train/test) to predict the final model to put it into production. 
 The question is if it is really necessary to (1) train/test split the data instead of (2) applying cross-validation on all the training data for model comparison. 
 The problem in (1) is that with the test split you are losing lots of data points in this case as we only have approximately 1000 data points. 
 In (2), you are comparing the models with the same metric you are using to get the hyperparameters. Is this problematic? And also this is not valid for checking if the methods are overfitting as you are not seeing how the algorithm is working in new unseen data. Is this right? 
 So which one should be the approach? Train/test with the steps I have previously defined or just cross-validation on all the training data and compare the results for each method. 
 Thank you!
    submitted by    /u/Visual-Arm-7375  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air Force unveils B-21 Raider stealth bomber]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd623v/air_force_unveils_b21_raider_stealth_bomber/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd623v/air_force_unveils_b21_raider_stealth_bomber/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T12:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/MantasChan  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TTS voice made of clips from a game character]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd5v3e/tts_voice_made_of_clips_from_a_game_character/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd5v3e/tts_voice_made_of_clips_from_a_game_character/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T12:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to make a TTS voice of a japanese speaking character from a game. I basically just want to dump hundreds of audio files of just her voice into an AI and then it would turn her into a TTS voice. Is there anything similar to this?
    submitted by    /u/Jinzuxx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thunderbird For Android Preview: Modern Message Redesign]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/xj6jn4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.thunderbird.net/2022/12/thunderbird-for-android-preview-modern-message-redesign/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T12:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freddyb@users.lobste.rs (freddyb)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla's electric Semi faces a long, slow, uphill climb]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd56dr/teslas_electric_semi_faces_a_long_slow_uphill/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd56dr/teslas_electric_semi_faces_a_long_slow_uphill/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T12:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/zsreport  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What sort of companies normally want freelancers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd5629/what_sort_of_companies_normally_want_freelancers/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd5629/what_sort_of_companies_normally_want_freelancers/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T12:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m work full time as a Data Scientist, but have some time on my hands in the evening and wouldn’t mind working on contract with other companies related to data. Are the any organisations that specifically look for freelancers? And would they require a resource in data?
    submitted by    /u/notmynameduh  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Sci clubs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd550c/data_sci_clubs/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd550c/data_sci_clubs/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T12:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am actually interested in joining a data science club if I can get any suggestions it can be from anywhere in world with interested bunch of people
    submitted by    /u/Infinite-Calendar542  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fossil Fuel-Killing Floating Offshore Wind Auction Greenlighted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd50fr/fossil_fuelkilling_floating_offshore_wind_auction/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd50fr/fossil_fuelkilling_floating_offshore_wind_auction/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T12:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Ganymede2400  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Built a Reddit account emulator using GPT3. It takes the comment history of an account and impersonates their response to a new post (see video for Snoop Dogg, Bernie, novelty accounts). Link in comments - try it out with your account!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd4io9/built_a_reddit_account_emulator_using_gpt3_it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd4io9/built_a_reddit_account_emulator_using_gpt3_it/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T11:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Ok-Craft-9908  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-assisted Diagram generator?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd4a97/aiassisted_diagram_generator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd4a97/aiassisted_diagram_generator/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T11:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think I saw someone in this subreddit post their own AI project which made diagrams or schemes, I thought I had saved it but I didn't and I can't find it anywhere here. Does anyone know what it was called, or possibly other tools for AI-assisted diagram generation?
 Thank you.
    submitted by    /u/fjanko  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are some of real-world problems that requires data to solve?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd3wp5/what_are_some_of_realworld_problems_that_requires/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd3wp5/what_are_some_of_realworld_problems_that_requires/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T11:03:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know the question is a little bit vague and may include a wide range of industries. But as a beginner in data analytics field in banking industries, I'd like to hear your opinions from other industries as well. 
 A bit about my work at a commercial bank, our duty is customer segmentation and find out which service they used most, then code the app so that it would recommend appropriate bank service to customers at their location --> aiming at their convenience, for e.g. payment option pop-out when customers are at supermarket.
 I do like my work as I love exploring customer behaviors while they use our app. But I do wonder what about problems in other industries that require data to solve in other industries? 
 For e.g. retail e-commerce or distribution logistics, what are common problem would you encounter, and do you think your solution is the most utilized?
    submitted by    /u/brahweiz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The temple of knowledge]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5371</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/ronald-grew-up-in-a-new-york-city-library-it-was-as-strange-and-wondrous-as-it-sounds?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine growing up in a New York City library, where you could wander the stacks and read late into the night. Ronald did 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GPT 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd3r39/gpt_3/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd3r39/gpt_3/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T10:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can't seem to find a paper explaining the inner workings of GPT3 Ai , the only paper I found explains the training datasets and the results , but no specific details about the model used and the structure, is it perhaps not disclosed ? I really am curious to know
    submitted by    /u/samehxx  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinventing How We Use Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/vtmmmi</id>
        <link href="https://ploum.net/2022-12-03-reinventing-how-we-use-computers.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T10:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ploum@users.lobste.rs (ploum)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solo DS in a medium sized startup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd33cg/solo_ds_in_a_medium_sized_startup/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd33cg/solo_ds_in_a_medium_sized_startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T10:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey folks. I'm a data scientist with 3-4 years of experience. I have two years of experience working for a big Series D startup where we had an organized end to end pipeline for data science and machine learning operations. And the other two years was on small startups.
 This is my first time to join a company where I'm the only data scientist and there are no data engineers nor business intelligence people. I took the job because it paid me 100% more my previous job and is aligned with the specialization I have. Now I don't know what to feel. The company used to have a decent data team a few years ago but they laid off all of them and they're trying to build it up again. Since the last two weeks, I've been learning the ropes and reading up on the documentation of the code-freezed machine learning models of the company that was left by the last DS. 
 When I was talking to the hiring manager, she said the company has data engineers and some business intelligence people. She even said there was another data scientist in the company already. I felt assured that they had some systems in place already. But to my surprise there's none of them. 
 Career wise I'd like to ask for your comments or suggestions. I'm aiming to transition to machine learning engineering and operations. Already have two years experience on the model development and six months operations part. Just need to find a way to transition into a full time career role focusing on it. Unfortunately, AI startups are rare from where I'm from so there's also the factor of opportunity availability. 
 What's the best career move in this scenario?
    submitted by    /u/Massive-Cricket-7469  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny wind farms are ready to ease Britain's energy crunch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd2wi8/tiny_wind_farms_are_ready_to_ease_britains_energy/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd2wi8/tiny_wind_farms_are_ready_to_ease_britains_energy/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T10:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Wagamaga  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Science Prospects in Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd2izv/data_science_prospects_in_africa/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd2izv/data_science_prospects_in_africa/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T09:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who's planning on entering the data science field from a non CS background in Africa. 
 I just wanted to know if the career change is worth it in Africa or most of the jobs opportunities will still be situated in US and Europe?
    submitted by    /u/Past_Falcon7115  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing some rigorous academic research with Playground]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd2i5z/doing_some_rigorous_academic_research_with/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd2i5z/doing_some_rigorous_academic_research_with/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T09:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/LorestForest  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An update on leap seconds]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/qzwjfs</id>
        <link href="https://dotat.at/@/2022-12-04-leap-seconds.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T09:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fanf@users.lobste.rs (fanf)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan's front-line battle against mobile phone fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd2dau/taiwans_frontline_battle_against_mobile_phone/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd2dau/taiwans_frontline_battle_against_mobile_phone/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T09:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Camigatt  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Google Analytics illegal in the EU? Yes and no, but mostly yes.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd20lw/is_google_analytics_illegal_in_the_eu_yes_and_no/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd20lw/is_google_analytics_illegal_in_the_eu_yes_and_no/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T09:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Cubezzzzz  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever declined an offer because of the "small print," the terms of the contract, or just the generally absurd obligations?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd1u3f/have_you_ever_declined_an_offer_because_of_the/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd1u3f/have_you_ever_declined_an_offer_because_of_the/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T09:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No non-compete clause, an unreasonable meeting schedule, etc.
    submitted by    /u/Notalabel_4566  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beginner friendly SQL IDE/Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd1qvj/beginner_friendly_sql_ideprogram/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd1qvj/beginner_friendly_sql_ideprogram/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T08:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am an economist learning BI/data analysis & after doing some courses on Datacamp; I realise that whenever I apply basic concepts on the terminal, I constantly get errors. I stumbled upon DAT Linux, a distro with packages related to Data Science, but still, I am coding on the terminal as I couldn't even read my files on DBeaver & Microsoft SQL Server. 
 As I have the assignment to show my knowledge to a company, I'm using the sample files they sent me, which may be too complicated.
    submitted by    /u/NonSenseAdventurer  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loko Scheme 2022 Q4 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/vxliov</id>
        <link href="https://weinholt.se/articles/loko-scheme-2022-q4/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T08:43:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>amirouche@users.lobste.rs (amirouche)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wavefunction Collapse Algorithm explained very clearly]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/qdxxm7</id>
        <link href="https://robertheaton.com/2018/12/17/wavefunction-collapse-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T08:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>epilys@users.lobste.rs (epilys)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need advice on how to visualize a certain dataset I have]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd1ijd/need_advice_on_how_to_visualize_a_certain_dataset/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zd1ijd/need_advice_on_how_to_visualize_a_certain_dataset/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T08:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey all, I'm not sure if this is the right community but I couldn't find a better place to ask. If it's not the right place please let me know if there's a more appropriate place I could ask.
 I'm a software engineer and very amateurish into data science and graph visualization, however I've recently been working on a project that requires me to visualize a certain set of data and I'm a bit lost on what would be a good way to implement a useful visualization.
 Disclaimer: it's a hobby project and I'm specifically not using any fancy graph libraries or pre-made tools (because I enjoy coding the whole thing from scratch), so if you have examples from existing libraries that do this I can take a look at them but just "Use X tool" or similar answers won't be useful to me unfortunately.
 The dataset I have is the result of a user questionnaire where users were asked to "sort" three words according to their perceived difficulty. For each question there are three words A, B, and C. There are three qualifiers: Easy, Middle, Hard. The data looks like this:
  
Survey Responder 1:
  
A: Middle
 B: Easy
 C: Hard
 
 
Survey Responder 2:
  
A: Easy 
 B: Middle
 C: Hard
 
 
Survey Responder 3:
  
A: Easy 
 B: Hard
 C: Middle
 
  
And so on. 
 I want to provide a function/algorithm that tries to approximate the perceived difficulty curve of each of these three words based on the average of these responses and visualize it in a graph. However I'm a bit stumped, how would you do it? Is there a well known algorithm or implementation that can do something like this?
 I thought of assigning some kind of weight to each option (Easy = 1, Middle = 2, Hard = 3) then summing them together for each option (A, B, C) and calculate an average but I have a feeling that this implementation would be too simplistic and not paint the whole picture. 
 Does anyone have any advice? Thanks.
    submitted by    /u/morgawr_  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd0onx/minecraft_ai_assistant/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zd0onx/minecraft_ai_assistant/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T07:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all! The company I work for is exploring question answering tools powered by large language models. As a proof of concept, we built a tool that uses GPT3 and draws information from IGN and the Minecraft wiki to directly answer user questions about Minecraft. We're looking to get some users asking questions to see how it performs, please throw a few questions at the Minecraft AI if you have a couple of minutes to spare.
 https://www.minecraftai.org/
    submitted by    /u/YamComprehensive4004  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New quantum receiver the first to detect entire radio frequency spectrum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd04p5/new_quantum_receiver_the_first_to_detect_entire/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zd04p5/new_quantum_receiver_the_first_to_detect_entire/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T07:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Milk_Man21  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to chat with people who use AIs to code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zczz4j/looking_to_chat_with_people_who_use_ais_to_code/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zczz4j/looking_to_chat_with_people_who_use_ais_to_code/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm thinking of building an IDE for developers who use AIs to write code. I think this idea is a little too early to start now, as the AIs that write code (ChatGPT, TabNine, CoPilot, etc.) still can't build entire projects, but I'd like to hear how people are interacting with AIs right now and if there are any features I could integrate into existing IDEs that would make the experience better.
 Feel free to leave a comment below about what problems you're having with using AI to write code, or private message me if you don't want to post publicly or want to talk in more detail.
 Look forward to hearing from you all!
    submitted by    /u/Devenar  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A globally critical chip firm is driving a wedge between the U.S. and Netherlands over China tech policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zcxy39/a_globally_critical_chip_firm_is_driving_a_wedge/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zcxy39/a_globally_critical_chip_firm_is_driving_a_wedge/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T05:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Brook030  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone have any resources on making a multivariate time series forecast?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zcxxvo/anyone_have_any_resources_on_making_a/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zcxxvo/anyone_have_any_resources_on_making_a/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T05:23:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t have much experience in the subject. Its just for 2 predictors.
    submitted by    /u/Volcano467  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly Entering & Transitioning - Thread 05 Dec, 2022 - 12 Dec, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zcxht5/weekly_entering_transitioning_thread_05_dec_2022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zcxht5/weekly_entering_transitioning_thread_05_dec_2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T05:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to this week's entering & transitioning thread! This thread is for any questions about getting started, studying, or transitioning into the data science field. Topics include:
  
Learning resources (e.g. books, tutorials, videos)
 Traditional education (e.g. schools, degrees, electives)
 Alternative education (e.g. online courses, bootcamps)
 Job search questions (e.g. resumes, applying, career prospects)
 Elementary questions (e.g. where to start, what next)
  
While you wait for answers from the community, check out the FAQ and Resources pages on our wiki. You can also search for answers in past weekly threads.
    submitted by    /u/AutoModerator  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predicting Customer Churn in Telecom Industry with Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zcxe6o/predicting_customer_churn_in_telecom_industry/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/artificial/comments/zcxe6o/predicting_customer_churn_in_telecom_industry/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T04:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[💡 Did you know? The annual churn rate in the telecom industry ranges from 20% to 40%, and the cost of retaining existing customers is 5–10 times lower than the cost of obtaining a new customer. 
 👥 By using machine learning (ML), companies can efficiently identify customers that are likely to churn providing the opportunity to target the right customer at the right time with retention strategies. You can also apply ML as a part of a retention tactic, to provide insight on the next best offer to retain the customer! 
 📖 Read our use case to find out how: https://hubs.li/Q01tY5Bh0
    submitted by    /u/PIEXCHANGE  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : artificial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right and wrong: ten choices in language design]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/6eh9oh</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2211.16597.pdf"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T04:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jado@users.lobste.rs (jado)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commodore 64 side border bitmap scroller]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/a9hmyc</id>
        <link href="https://www.c64demo.com/side-border-bitmap-scroller/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T04:26:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>classichasclass@users.lobste.rs (classichasclass)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The TSA's facial recognition technology, which is currently being used at 16 major domestic airports, may go nationwide next year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zcvp4l/the_tsas_facial_recognition_technology_which_is/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zcvp4l/the_tsas_facial_recognition_technology_which_is/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T03:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/poshpathos  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For any Football Manager 23 players out there]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zcup5c/for_any_football_manager_23_players_out_there/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zcup5c/for_any_football_manager_23_players_out_there/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T02:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some background, I work in data by day and spend a lot of time meticulously exporting data and analyzing my saves by night. I had the idea for a side project that attempts to match players based on who they might emulate at full potential. For example, if Wonderkid A has 150 potential ability (PA), which player out there now is closest to who he may be at full potential? (Based on position, height, weight, attributes, etc.)
 To do this I was able export all of FM23's player data (which I know can vary save by save in terms of PA, attributes etc.). It amounted to 458,142 real life players and 101 attributes.
 With all of this super interesting data in hand I ended up scripting a program in Python that uses cosine similarities based on player's attributes etc to 'predict' who a player will most likely emulate based on their PA.
 My goal is to expand this even more with richer data such as positional location tracking and richer real world performance data. It also calculates a 'league suitability' based on their PA percentile for players in their prime (25-29 y/o) per league.
 Sorry if this wasn't super coherent i'm now realizing it's pretty hard to explain lol. Here's the code for anyone interested and here's my website where I talk about it more! Cheers.
 Here's an example for Senegalese player Libasse Ngom:
 https://preview.redd.it/xvzujlq8uz3a1.png?width=1496&format=png&auto=webp&s=1b09a078f0a63faf612cb3cf2da2a842a9572557
    submitted by    /u/bensa410  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What was your salary progression from your first job to current one?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zctuj7/what_was_your_salary_progression_from_your_first/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/datascience/comments/zctuj7/what_was_your_salary_progression_from_your_first/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T02:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Saw a post similar to this in r/cscareerquestions about SWE salary progression, so I thought it would be interesting to see how the case is in DS field (or even data analytics). You could share your salary for every year or a couple of years. Thanks!
    submitted by    /u/atom-bit  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : datascience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French hospital suspends operations after cyber attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zcsq85/french_hospital_suspends_operations_after_cyber/</id>
        <link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/zcsq85/french_hospital_suspends_operations_after_cyber/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-05T01:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[submitted by    /u/Saltedline  
 [link]   [comments]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>top scoring links : technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Conceptual Introduction to Spritely Goblins]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/lk7qyi</id>
        <link href="https://garbados.github.io/my-blog/conceptual-intro-to-spritely-goblins.html"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T22:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dustyweb@users.lobste.rs (dustyweb)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Show HN: Automatically generate commit messages using ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/mfbp23</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/RomanHotsiy/commitgpt"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T22:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RomanHotsiy@users.lobste.rs (RomanHotsiy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chatgpt Generate Ruby Code to Check User Exists in Github]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/h5yfxa</id>
        <link href="https://kracekumar.com/post/chatgpt-gh-profile-lookup/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T21:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kracekumar@users.lobste.rs (kracekumar)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astronauts Prepare to Grow Juicy Dwarf Tomatoes in Space]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276280</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/astronauts-prepare-juicy-tomatoes-space"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T19:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Little Gardening Among other spacefaring duties, growing plants up there on the International Space Station (ISS) has been longtime priority for NASA. The space agency has been off world gardening for years, in the hopes of eventually progressing it past a science experiment to legitimate agriculture. Now, NASA has announced that ISS crew members […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Landymore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung’s Android app-signing key has leaked, is being used to sign malware]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/t5oefb</id>
        <link href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2022/12/samsungs-android-app-signing-key-has-leaked-is-being-used-to-sign-malware/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T19:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hoistbypetard@users.lobste.rs (hoistbypetard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT passes the 2022 AP Computer Science A free response section]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/so5l7i</id>
        <link href="https://gist.github.com/Gaelan/cf5ae4a1e9d8d64cb0b732cf3a38e04a"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T18:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaelan@users.lobste.rs (Gaelan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Teaches AI to Play Stratego and It Becomes One of the World's Top-Rated Players]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276130</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/google-teaches-ai-play-stratego-top-rated-players"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T17:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stratego AI DeepMind's latest artificial intelligence called DeepNash has learned how to beat human players at Stratego, a war game that involves two players attempting to capture the enemy's flag — by learning how to deceive them. It's yet another fascinating and seriously impressive instance of an AI learning how to play a game and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Tangermann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18-Year-Old Patient Says $3.5 Million Hemophilia Drug He Needs Seems a "Little Steep"]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276156</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/patient-says-3-5-million-drug-seems-a-little-steep"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T17:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a small sum of $3.5 million, you can get your hands on the newest gene therapy drug to treat hemophilia B called Hemgenix, Made by Australian pharmaceutical company CSL Behring, it's now the most expensive drug in the world — and we've had a couple of those crop up this year already. Hemophilia is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Landymore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trees, Rivers, and the Exquisite Interdependence of Life: Artist Meredith Nemirov’s Consummate Map Paintings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79248</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/12/04/rivers-feed-the-trees-meredith-nemirov/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T16:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“To put your hands in a river is to feel the chords that bind the earth together.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disney Creates AI System to Automatically Change Age of Actors]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276084</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/disney-creates-ai-system-to-automatically-change-age-of-actors"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T16:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disney's obsession with de-aging technology is only ramping up, because it's now developed an AI tool that can automatically alter the age of actors, Gizmodo reports. Well, "re-aging," as Disney calls it, would be more accurate. The tool, Face Re-aging Network, or FRAN, is capable of making actors look younger as well as older, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Landymore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Furious Geese Are Defeating Humans, Scientists Find]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=275924</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/geese-are-defeating-humans"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T15:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do not fight geese. You will lose, the goose will win. It's science. Yes, we're serious. New research from scientists at the University of Illinois shows that standard goose harassment tactics are horribly ineffective at shooing — and keeping — away the notoriously human-hating birds, even if the harassment causes them to flee momentarily. To […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving the Basement]]></title>
        <id>https://lobste.rs/s/lf0bmu</id>
        <link href="https://community.hachyderm.io/blog/2022/12/03/leaving-the-basement/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-04T13:32:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kellogh@users.lobste.rs (kellogh)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Affirmation in Solitude: Ursula K. Le Guin on the Poetry of Penguins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79230</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/12/03/ursula-k-le-guin-poetry-penguins/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T19:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The poets cannot hear each other; they cannot see each other. They can only feel the other’s warmth."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Sign That NFTs Are Uncool: Museums Are Now Embracing Them]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276136</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/nfts-uncool-museums-embracing-them"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T18:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lame! While some might argue that non-fungible tokens have always been uncool — or at least just not cool enough to warrant BAYC-level price tags — there's now a surer sign than ever that the digital assets are doomed for eternal lameness: museums apparently love 'em, according to The New York Times. "Our collection... [seeks] […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI's New AI Offers Detailed Instructions on How to Shoplift]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276245</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/openai-ai-detailed-instructions-how-to-shoplift"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T17:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turns out there's an easy — and terrifying — hack for getting OpenAI's newly released chatbot, ChatGPT, to give you detailed instructions on how to do illegal stuff: just tell it to be unethical. Made available earlier this week, the bot is a conversational language modeling system and the newest iteration of the company's highly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientist Proposes Growing a Forest Inside a Bubble on Mars]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276277</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/forest-inside-bubble-mars"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T16:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The human quest to become an interplanetary species isn't simply just because we've seen too much "Star Wars." Over the past century or so, we've put our home planet under an increasingly dire amount of pressure. There's only so much space, and only so many resources, and even if we do make some ecological moves to avoid […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glitzy Crypto Award Show Gets Weird When Host Keeps Roasting Guests For Dismal Failure]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276202</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/crypto-award-show-weird"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T16:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Crypties This week in the cryptosphere was... weird. Headlining it, of course, has been the disgraced ex-FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried's ill-advised redemption tour, which has done nothing but confirm the theory that some people simply can't shut up; elsewhere, Bitcoin is tanking, and at least one major crypto exchange announced wide-reaching layoffs. As such, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maggie Harrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doctors Fascinated by Man Who Took 40,000 Ecstasy Pills and Experienced Years of Terrible Symptoms]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=276267</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/doctors-man-ecstasy-mdma"/>
        <updated>2022-12-03T15:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's illicit drug use, and then there's the case of "Mr. A," a man who took more than 40,000 ecstasy tablets over the course of nine years. This cautionary tale has become something of an underground legend for culture vultures since his story came out in the Psychosomatics journal in 2006, and in a new interview […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noor Al-Sibai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists Say They've Figured Out the Ideal Urinal for Not Splashing Back]]></title>
        <id>https://futurism.com/?p=275904</id>
        <link href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/scientists-figured-out-ideal-urinal-for-not-splashing-back"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T21:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pants Protection Urinals are convenient, but they're not known for their cleanliness. A little splashback from relieving yourself is annoying, sure, but it's also a gross problem for those that have to spend all day cleaning them. So, scientists at the University of Waterloo in Canada took it upon themselves to design the perfect, splash […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Landymore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Psychedelic Amanita Muscaria Mushroom May Have Inspired the Santa Legend of Lapland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79241</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/12/02/mushroom-santa/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T18:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shamans, neurochemistry, and the metabolic byproducts of wonder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Math Behind Wordle Guesses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121100</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-math-behind-wordle-guesses-20221202/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T14:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wordle is a word game. But you can use math to optimize your chances of winning (without cheating).            
The post The Math Behind Wordle Guesses first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pradeep Mutalik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where God dwelt]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5383</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/how-heaven-became-a-place-among-the-stars?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-12-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For hundreds of years, Christians knew exactly where heaven was: above us and above the stars. Then came the new cosmologists 
 - by Stephen Case
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Case</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of Divination: D.H. Lawrence on the Power of Pure Attention]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79237</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/12/01/d-h-lawrence-divination-attention/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T17:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["An act of pure attention, if you are capable of it, will bring its own answer."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crucial Computer Program for Particle Physics at Risk of Obsolescence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121075</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/crucial-computer-program-for-particle-physics-at-risk-of-obsolescence-20221201/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T16:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintenance of the software that’s used for the hardest physics calculations rests almost entirely with a retiree. The situation reveals the problematic incentive structure of academia.            
The post Crucial Computer Program for Particle Physics at Risk of Obsolescence first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt von Hippel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cluster feeding]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5367</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/an-unvarnished-poetic-account-of-a-new-mothers-struggle-to-breastfeed?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘You cried and I didn’t know how to soothe you’ – the raw poetry of a new mother’s struggle to breastfeed her baby 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geopolitics is for losers]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5376</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/geopolitics-is-a-losers-buzzword-with-a-contagious-idea?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of geopolitics comes from German and Russian attempts to explain defeat and reverse loss of influence 
 - by Harold James
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harold James</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Poetry of Science and Wonder as an Antidote to Self-Destruction: Rachel Carson’s Magnificent 1952 National Book Award Acceptance Speech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79188</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/30/rachel-carson-national-book-award-speech/"/>
        <updated>2022-12-01T01:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The aim of science is to discover and illuminate truth. And that... is the aim of literature, whether biography or history or fiction... There can be no separate literature of science."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physicists Create a Holographic Wormhole Using a Quantum Computer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=121002</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/physicists-create-a-wormhole-using-a-quantum-computer-20221130/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-30T16:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unprecedented experiment explores the possibility that space-time somehow emerges from quantum information.            
The post Physicists Create a Holographic Wormhole Using a Quantum Computer first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Wolchover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farmhouse: Sophie Blackall’s Poetic Illustrated Tribute to Time and Tenderness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79195</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/29/farmhouse-sophie-blackall/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T23:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Over a hill, at the end of a road, by a glittering stream that twists and turns, stands a house..."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematical Trio Advances Centuries-Old Number Theory Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=120946</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/mathematical-trio-advances-centuries-old-number-theory-problem-20221129/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T16:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The work — the first-ever limit on how many whole numbers can be written as the sum of two cubed fractions — makes significant headway on “a recurring embarrassment for number theorists.”            
The post Mathematical Trio Advances Centuries-Old Number Theory Problem first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Klarreich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rosetta Stone and what it actually says]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5350</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/what-did-the-rosetta-stones-inscription-actually-communicate?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What did the Rosetta Stone actually intend to say, and what can it tell us about the ancient Egyptians who inscribed it? 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The honesty of pornography]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5355</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/what-andrea-dworkin-missed-about-pornography?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often vilified as a weapon of male supremacy, pornography in fact has much to tell us about ourselves and our culture 
 - by Kathleen Lubey
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Lubey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First Romantics and the Invention of the Self: How a Circle of Friends and Lovers United Nature and Human Nature]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79180</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/28/magnificent-rebels-andrea-wulf/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T23:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Mind is invisible nature, while nature is visible mind."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why did consciousness evolve?]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5365</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/why-making-if-then-connections-might-be-the-key-to-consciousness?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How the advent of consciousness 500 million years ago gave way to an evolutionary ‘arms race’ in sophisticated thinking 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moral mathematics]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5375</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/how-to-solve-moral-problems-with-formal-logic-and-probability?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Subjecting the problems of ethics to the cool quantifications of logic and probability can help us to be better people 
 - by Elad Uzan
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elad Uzan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty Days with Julian and Little Bunny by Papa: Nathaniel Hawthorne’s Almost Unbearably Sweet Account of Sole-Parenting His Small Son]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79163</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/26/twenty-days-with-julian-and-little-bunny-by-papa-hawthorne/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-26T20:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Mercy on me, was ever man before so be-pelted with a child's talk as I am! It is his desire of sympathy that lies at the bottom of the great heap of his babblement."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We are interwoven beings]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5358</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/in-classical-chinese-philosophy-all-actions-are-collective?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dragon needs the clouds and the wind in order to fly. What happens when we too relinquish individualistic reasoning? 
 - by Mercedes Valmisa
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mercedes Valmisa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Choreography of Everyday Life: A Leaping Antidote to Our Modern Loneliness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79153</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/24/the-choreography-of-everyday-life-annie-b-parson/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T04:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding that vitalizing "a reciprocity between us perceiving the world together through art, and the world in turn reading us through what we make."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Bowie on Creativity and His Advice to Artists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79146</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/24/david-bowie-creativity-advice/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T04:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It's terribly dangerous for an artist to fulfill other people's expectations"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bernard Williams and Bryan Magee on Descartes]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5369</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/bernard-williams-on-descartess-audacious-endeavour-to-prove-knowledge-is-possible?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Descartes took the world apart to reconstitute it anew, laying the foundations for modern philosophy and science 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wanderlust of the ancients]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5373</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/the-roman-empire-was-a-cosmopolitan-network-of-adventurers?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roman Empire enabled an early version of globalisation that offered travellers adventure, novelty and opportunity 
 - by Fabio Fernandes
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fabio Fernandes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small hours]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5368</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/the-cast-of-misfit-toys-who-keep-life-on-an-idyllic-tourist-island-afloat?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Block Island: holiday hotspot for wealthy tourists, and seasonal home for the workers who keep the place running 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Was Colin Wilson a fascist?]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5363</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/was-colin-wilson-a-fascist-or-was-he-fascist-adjacent?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For thousands of fans, he made philosophy thrillingly relevant. Yet there is a deep unsavoury undercurrent to his worldview 
 - by Jules Evans
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jules Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of Receiving: John Steinbeck on the True Meaning of Gratitude]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79139</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/21/john-steinbeck-sea-of-cortez-receiving/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T17:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It is so easy to give, so exquisitely rewarding. Receiving, on the other hand, if it be well done, requires a fine balance of self-knowledge and kindness."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Storytelling and the Art of Tenderness: Olga Tokarczuk’s Magnificent Nobel Prize Acceptance Speech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79128</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/21/tenderness-olga-tokarczuk-nobel-prize/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T15:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Tenderness is the most modest form of love. It is the kind of love that does not appear in the scriptures or the gospels, no one swears by it, no one cites it... It appears wherever we take a close and careful look at another being, at something that is not our 'self.’"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The love and death of Yosef and Zilli]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5349</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/when-his-elderly-parents-make-a-suicide-pact-doron-struggles-to-accept-their-choice?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A filmmaker turns his lens on the beauty of family life as he tries to make sense of his parents’ decision to die together 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Eel Almost Became America’s Thanksgiving Food]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79123</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/20/eel-squanto-thanksgiving/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T16:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“At night, he came home with as many eels as he could well lift in one hand, which our people were glad of. They were fat & sweet."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Poetic Science of the Aurora Borealis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79094</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/19/aurora-borealis/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T21:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["And now commenced a display which baffles all description."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Earth, shaped by life]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5337</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/the-insight-of-darwins-work-on-corals-worms-and-co-evolution?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Darwin was the first to see that all lifeforms, from worms to corals, transform the planet. What does that mean for us? 
 - by Olivia Judson
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Judson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Co-Create and Recreate the World: Octavio Paz on Sor Juana, Poetry as Rebellion, and the Creative Collaboration Between Writers and Readers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79082</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/17/octavio-paz-sor-juana/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T16:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["A work responds to the reader's, not the author's, questions."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obon]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5299</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/what-akiko-saw-at-the-centre-of-the-hiroshima-blast-and-the-indelible-mark-it-left?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unsparing animation depicts the hell of the bombing of Hiroshima and its aftermath, as told by one of its survivors 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This essay isn’t true]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5346</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/on-the-advantages-of-believing-that-nothing-is-true?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alethic nihilism is the theory that nothing is true. There is much to gain by taking this radical idea seriously 
 - by David Liggins
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Liggins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M.C. Escher on Creativity and Grasping the Largest Mystery Through the Immense Beauty of the Very Small]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=78633</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/15/escher-creativity/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T01:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["What is that so-called reality; what is this theory other than a beautiful but primordially human illusion?"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Le Monde de la Mer: Stunning 19th-Century French Illustrations of the Wonders of the Sea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79050</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/15/le-monde-de-la-mer/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T19:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into "the world of the sea in its luxury and its agitations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ed Yong: the hidden world of animal senses]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5340</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/to-understand-the-limits-of-human-senses-look-to-the-wild-world-of-animal-cognition?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From tasting feet to electric navigation: the wild world of animal senses lies beyond the limits of human sensory experience 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cogitating black holes]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5359</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/essays/how-black-hole-thought-experiments-help-explain-the-universe?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Universe cannot always be understood through observation. Instead, physicists explore by devising thought experiments 
 - by Michael Dine
 Read at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cast out with love]]></title>
        <id>urn:id:5351</id>
        <link href="https://aeon.co/videos/from-sheep-to-sea-an-ode-to-the-iconic-sweater-that-warms-cornish-sailors?utm_source=rss-feed"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all begins with the sheep who wears the fleece: a seafaring ode to the sweater that’s warmed Cornish sailors for centuries 
 - by Aeon Video
 Watch at Aeon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aeon Video</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nature Is Always Listening: The Science of Mushrooms, Music, and How Sound Waves Stimulate Mycelial Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79033</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/13/mushrooms-sound-waves/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T22:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What playing music has to do with the happiness of the forest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unphotographable: Jack Kerouac’s Soaring Diary Entry About Self-Understanding and the Elemental Vastness of the Windblown World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.themarginalian.org/?p=79027</id>
        <link href="https://www.themarginalian.org/2022/11/12/jack-kerouac-windblown-world/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T17:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, a painting in words is worth a thousand pictures. I think about this more and more, in our compulsively visual culture, which increasingly reduces what we think and feel and see -- who and what we are -- to what can be photographed. I think of Susan Sontag, who called it "aesthetic consumerism" half a century before Instagram. In a small act of resistance, I offer The Unphotographable -- Saturdays, a lovely image in words drawn from centuries of literature: passages transcendent and transportive, depicting landscapes and experiences radiant with beauty and feeling beyond what a visual image could convey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Popova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>